Guide to the Gerrit Lansing Papers YCAL MSS 469
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 2019 acquisition, 1814–2018; Bulk, 1950–2018; 8; 53.85 Linear Feet (66 boxes)
  - Personal Papers
    - Photographs
      - Poets and friends, 1960–2013 (Box 58)
        Includes photographs of John Wieners, Mark Nunnelee, David Maitland, Chuck Stein, Don Byrd, John Mulrooney, Ken Irby, Maurice Pollinet, Sabra Loomis, Tom Zajkowski, and Ricardo Cazares.
      - Portraits of Lansing, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 58)
        Photographs of Lansing by John Latouche, and photos of him as a child.
      - Scott/Lansing family photos and photos of heirlooms, 1900-circa 2000 (Box 58)
      - Thorpe Feidt paintings, 2007?; 2 Folders (Box 58)
      - Unidentified portraits: man, New York City; young boy, possibly Charles B. Lansing, Cleveland, Ohio, undated (Box 58)
      - Alice Scott Lansing and Charles B. Lansing, Jr., [triple-hinged photograph frame], circa 1900 (Box 46)
      - Two portraits, probably Lansing's parents [double-hinged frame], circa 1911? (Box 46)
      - Two photographs of unidentified woman [green double-hinged frame] (Box 46)
      - Unidentified woman on a horse, man in military uniform [small rhinestone frame], circa 1918? (Box 46)
      - Mother's Aunt Josephine, mother's younger sister, circa 1890? (Box 46)
      - Alice Scott Lansing at nine months old [small green velvet case], 1855
    - Artwork and Unique Books
      Contains several collages by Lansing, and artwork and books gifted to Lansing, including a collection of broadsides created by various writers, artists, and friends for his 75th birthday.
      Arranged alphabetically by folder title, with materials from "Gerrit's Birthday Box" filed at the end of the sequence.
      - Art and birthday broadsides, 1978-2009, undated (Box 59)
      - Artwork by friends, 1985–2015 (Box 60)
      - Bialy, Harvey, "Shemesh", undated (Box 59)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 59)
        - Christmas card, illustrated poem, 1966-1967, undated
        - "Earth's Winter Song", 1965
      - Doane, Timotha, note enclosed with broadside [broadside missing], 2014 (Box 59)
      - Elmslie, Kenward, untitled volume of poetry and collage for Lansing's 70th birthday, 1998 (Box 61)
      - Irby, Ken, "[homage to Josephine Baker]", 2011 (Box 60)
      - Kelly, Ellsworth, L'Amour Fou by Andre Breton, undated (Box 60)
        Inscribed by Kelly as "Souvenir de Paris" for Lansing in 1958.
      - Lansing, Gerrit, "A Boke from Dogtown", undated (Box 60)
        Folio of postcards.
      - Lansing, Gerrit, collages, undated (Box 59)
      - "Gerrit's Birthday Box", 2002–2003
        "Gerrit's Birthday Box" is a collection of signed broadsides gifted to Lansing on his 75th birthday in a decorative box. Includes collages, drawings, paintings, photographs, and poetry.
        - Contributors (Box 62)
        - Abel, David (Box 62)
        - Alcaly, Ammiel (Box 62)
        - Amory, Rob (Box 62)
        - Anastas, Peter (Box 62)
        - Barrett, Ed (Box 62)
        - Bee, Susan, and Charles Bernstein (Box 62)
        - Behrle, Jim (Box 63)
        - Bialy, Harvey (Box 63)
        - Blair, Richard, and Jed Hickson (Box 63)
        - Bouchard, Daniel, and Kate Nugent (Box 63)
        - Chapman, Lee (Box 63)
        - Clay, Steve, and Julie Harrison (Box 63)
        - Cole, Sean (Box 63)
        - Cook, Amanda (Box 63)
        - Cook, James (Box 63)
        - Corbett, Beverly (Box 63)
        - Corbett, William (Box 63)
        - Cross, Del Ray (Box 63)
        - Doud, Ariane (Box 63)
        - Doud, Patrick (Box 63)
        - Dunn, Jim (Box 63)
        - Eshleman, Clayton (Box 63)
        - Evans, Jack (Box 63)
        - Feidt, Thorpe (Box 63)
        - Ferrini, Vincent (Box 63)
        - Franco, Michael (Box 63)
        - Freilicher, Jane (Box 63)
        - Gardner, Drew (Box 63)
        - Gruttola, Raffael de (Box 63)
        - Harrison, Jim (Box 63)
        - Iijima, Brenda (Box 63)
        - Irby, Ken (Box 63)
        - Joris, Pierre (Box 63)
        - Kelly, Robert (Box 63)
        - Killian, Kevin (Box 63)
        - King, Brian (Box 63)
        - Ligorano, Nora, and Marshall Reese (Box 63)
        - Lombardo, Stanley (Box 63)
        - Lyons, Kimberly (Box 63)
        - McNaughton, Duncan (Box 63)
        - Meyer, Thomas (Box 63)
        - Mlinko, Ange (Box 63)
        - Movius, Geoffrey (Box 63)
        - Norris, Rob (Box 63)
        - Pettet, Simon (Box 63)
        - Podgurski, Robert (Box 63)
        - Pruitt, Patricia (Box 63)
        - Raworth, Tom (Box 63)
        - Ryan, Paul (Box 63)
        - Sanders, Ed (Box 63)
        - Sandy, Stephen (Box 63)
        - Sawyer-Lauçanno, Christopher (Box 63)
        - Scotti, Steve (Box 63)
        - Shively, Charles (Box 63)
        - Smith, Dale (Box 63)
        - Smith, Marla (Box 63)
        - Smith, Pat (Box 63)
        - Stein, Charles (Box 63)
        - Stephens, Joseph (Box 63)
        - Strauss, David Levi (Box 63)
        - Strong, Jonathan, and Scott Elledge (Box 63)
        - Thompson, Ashley (Box 63)
        - Torra, Joe (Box 63)
        - Watkins, Ben E. (Box 63)
        - Weston, Carol (Box 63)
        - Wieners, John (Box 63)
        - Wigutow, Warren (Box 63)
        - Wilson, Peter Lamborn (Box 63)
        - Unidentified (Box 63)
        - Box designed and constructed by Judy Beenk (Box 64)
    - Music
      Includes autograph manuscript and printed music by Kenward Elmslie, Ben Weber, and Elie Yarden, often inscribed to Lansing, and a manuscript of "Festival Song (the New Year)," a collaboration with Yarden featuring Lansing's poetry.
      Arranged alphabetically by creator surname.
      - Cooper, D. F., autograph manuscript sheet music, 1904-1928? (Box 59)
      - Elmslie, Kenward, and Donald Fuller, "Thirty-Love" overture, undated (Box 59)
      - Elmslie, Kenward, and John Gruen, "Adele the Vaudeville Martinet," inscribed to Lansing, 1960 (Box 59)
      - Lansing, Gerrit, autograph manuscript sheet music, undated (Box 59)
      - Latouche, John, and Donald Fuller, various compositions, including original manuscript of Fuller's "Dance Variations in the Form of a Chacone", 1938–1939 (Box 59)
      - Weber, Ben (Box 59)
        - "Five Bagatelles for Piano," inscribed to Lansing, 1958
        - "Humoreske," dedicated to Lansing, original manuscript and printed sheet music, annotated, 1958
        - "Intermezzo", 1972
        - "Two Songs, Op. 63," inscribed to Lansing, 1972
        - "Variazioni Quasi Una Fantasia, Op. 54," inscribed to Lansing, 1974
      - Yarden, Elie (Box 59)
        - "Festival Song (the New Year)", 1966
        - "Two Bagatelles for GYL," inscribed to Lansing, 1957
        - "Two Moods", 1957
  - Stephen Jonas Papers
    This subseries contains notebooks and poetry drafts by Jonas and a small amount of original correspondence with Gerrit Lansing, dating from 1955 until Jonas's death in 1970, as well as printed versions of his poems. There are also materials related to posthumous tributes, memorials, and publications, and a collection of books owned by Jonas.
    Organized into four groupings: Notebooks, Correspondence, Writings and Other Papers, and Printed Materials.
    - Notebooks
      Notebooks contain poems and short autobiographies, as well as writings by Jonas on capitalism, jazz, politicians, racism and civil rights, culture, religion, and international relations. They also include notes on readings and the occult, addresses of people and businesses, and copies of letters by Jonas to Lansing and other friends.
      - Untitled notebook, 1962 (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebook, 1962–1963 (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebook, 1963 (Box 65)
      - "Writings", 1963–1964 (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebook, 1964 (Box 65)
      - "Journal", 1964–1965 (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebooks, 1965; 2 Folders (Box 65)
      - "Ars Magna, Stephen Jonas, Initiate", 1966 (Box 66)
      - Untitled notebooks, 1966; 4 Folders (Box 65)
      - "Writers and their work", 1966–1967 (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebook, 1967–1968 (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebooks, 1968; 2 Folders (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebooks, 1969; 3 Folders (Box 65)
      - "Conduct-92", undated (Box 65)
      - "English", undated (Box 65)
      - "A Notebook - Bale Lanbers", undated (Box 65)
        In addition to Jonas's writings, there are notes in an unknown hand, probably the original owner of the notebook.
      - Untitled notebooks, undated; 3 Folders (Box 65)
      - Untitled notebooks, undated; 2 Folders (Box 67)
    - Correspondence
      Contains original correspondence between Lansing and Jonas, and photocopies of outgoing letters from Jonas, possibly created by one or both of his literary executors, Lansing and Raffael de Gruttola. Topics of letters include Jonas's writings and personal matters, such as a 1963 verdict in a case against him brought by the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.
      - Letters to Raffael de Gruttola, 1967 [photocopies], undated (Box 67)
      - Letters to LeRoi Jones (Amiri Baraka), 1961-1963 [photocopies], undated (Box 67)
      - Lansing, Gerrit
        - Letters from Jonas, 1961–1967 (Box 67)
        - Letters to Jonas, 1961-1964, undated (Box 67)
      - Letters to various recipients, 1960-1968 [photocopies], circa 2000 (Box 67)
        Contains copies of letters from Jonas to writers and editors, including Cid Corman, Robert Kelly, and John Wieners. One letter is attached to a noted, dated 2000, by Raffael de Gruttola.
    - Other Writings and Papers
      Includes original and photocopied drafts of poems and other writings by Jonas, in addition to materials related to his death and posthumous publication of his works.
      - Death certificate, FOIA request, 1993 (Box 67)
      - Drafts, typescript and autograph manuscript, 1960-1965, undated (Box 67)
      - Drafts, typescript, 1955–1967 (Box 67)
      - Drafts, typescript, undated; 11 Folders (Box 67)
      - Joe Torra notebook regarding publication of Jonas's works, circa 1994 (Box 67)
      - The Magazine of Further Studies, inscribed by Jonas and Duncan McNaughton, 1967 (Box 67)
      - Materials related to Jonas publications, 1957–1994 (Box 67)
      - Permissions correspondence, 1989–2001 (Box 67)
      - Photocopies of Jonas correspondence, writings, 1996 (Box 67)
        Includes letters to Jonas from Duncan McNaughton, George Stanley, and Andrew Crozier.
      - Photocopies of published poems by Jonas, undated (Box 67)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 67)
        Includes a photograph of Jonas with two unidentified men, and photographs of Jonas alone and with a cigarette, as well as a portrait of an unidentified woman.
      - Reviews of and essays on Jonas, 1970-1974, undated (Box 67)
      - Tributes, memorials, circa 1970-2012 (Box 67)
      - Writings by Jack Spicer and Joe Dunn, 1956 [photocopies], undated (Box 67)
    - Printed Materials
      Publications featuring poetry by Jonas or writings about him, and a collection of books and serials from Jonas's personal library.
      Organized into two sub-groupings: Works by or about Jonas, and Works Collected by Jonas.
      - Works by or about Jonas
        Includes individual poems and poetry collections by Jonas that were published during his lifetime and posthumously, and journal issues dedicated to Jonas and his works.
        - The Music Master, 1965 (Box 68)
        - Exercises for Ear [hardcover], 1968 (Box 68)
        - "Exercises for Ear" [booklet], 1968 (Box 68)
        - "The Spring & Summer Annual", 1968 (Box 68)
        - Morphogenesis: (being a conventionalization of "Morphemes" of Jack Spicer), 1970 (Box 68)
        - Two for Jack Spicer, 1974 (Box 68)
        - lift, double issue, numbers 10 & 11, "Stephen Jonas", 1992 (Box 68)
        - Atelier, Vol. 2, No. 6 [writings about Jonas], 1992 (Box 68)
        - :that:, issue #23 [contains four letters by Jonas to other writers], 1994 (Box 68)
        - Selected Poems of Stephen Jonas, 1994 (Box 68)
        - "ah hum" [broadside printed by Jeff Conant], 1996 (Box 66)
      - Works Collected by Jonas
        Includes books and serials containing poetry or occult themes, most of which bear Jonas's signature or ownership stamp.
        Arranged alphabetically by author.
        - Dowson, Ernest Christopher. The Complete Lyrics of Ernest Dowson (Box 68)
        - Hartmann, Franz. The Life of Paracelsus (Box 69 (Oversize))
        - Langton, Edward. Essentials of Demonology (Box 69 (Oversize))
        - Mathers, S. L. McGregor. The Tarot: Its Occult Signification (Box 68)
        - McCaffery, Ellen. Graphic Astrology: The Astrological Home Study Course (Box 69 (Oversize))
        - Pound, Ezra. ABC of Reading (Box 69 (Oversize))
        - Taylor, Thomas. Eleusinian and Bacchic Mysteries (Box 69 (Oversize))
        - Waite, Arthur Edward.
          - The Hidden Church of the Holy Graal (Box 69 (Oversize))
          - The Holy Kabbalah (Box 69 (Oversize))
        - Hudson Review: Confucian Analects (Box 68)
        - Origin, Summer 1953; Autumn 1953 (Box 68)
  - Deryk Burton Papers
    Deryk Burton (1931-1997), a yacht captain, was born in England and emigrated to the United States. He was Gerrit Lansing's partner for almost 40 years and helped operate Abraxas Bookstore, which Lansing opened in 1982 in Gloucester.
    This subseries contains correspondence between Gerrit Lansing and Deryk Burton, as well as personal, financial, and legal papers of Burton.
    - Letters from Burton to Lansing, 1967; 1986; undated (Box 70)
    - Letters from Lansing to Burton
      - 1961–1969 (Box 70)
      - 1973–1979 (Box 70)
      - 1981-1988, undated (Box 70)
    - Correspondence with family and friends, 1950–1975 (Box 70)
    - Employment and financial, 1947–1993 (Box 70)
    - Personal documents, naturalization, passports, death certificate, 1956–1997 (Box 70)
    - Seaman's documents, 1948–1980 (Box 70)
    - Writings, undated (Box 70)
  - John McGavern Papers
    John McGavern (1926-2008) was director of the University of Hartford library system in Connecticut for 34 years. Born in Arlington, Massachusetts, McGavern graduated from Harvard University in 1949, and later received a master's degree in library science from Simmons College in 1959. He met and befriended Gerrit Lansing while both men were students at Harvard.
    This subseries contains drafts of poems and other writings by John McGavern and correspondence with Gerrit Lansing. Lansing's letters to McGavern are sometimes enclosed with his poems. There is also one manuscript by Douglas Stafford, a Black high school English teacher and McGavern's partner for over 25 years.
    - Binder 1 [poems, autograph manuscript and typescript], 1959-1984, undated (Box 71)
    - Binder 2 - "Fragments" [poems, autograph manuscript and typescript], 1947–1956; 2 Folders (Box 71)
    - Binder 3 - "Hunting in Vermont and other poems by John McGavern", undated (Box 71)
    - De Heredia, José-Maria, Les Trophées, annotated by McGavern, 1955 (Box 71)
    - Drafts, typescript and autograph manuscript, 1945–1984; 7 Folders (Box 71)
      Contains drafts of poetry and other works by McGavern, including an autobiography and a play he wrote for his partner Douglas Stafford's students at Rutland High School in Vermont, notes, drawings, and outlines, a small amount of printed material, and several rejection letters from publishers.
    - Drafts, typescript and autograph manuscript, 1945–1984; 5 Folders (Box 72)
    - Letters from Lansing to McGavern, 1946–1966; 2 Folders (Box 72)
    - Letters from McGavern to Lansing, 1982, undated (Box 72)
    - A Manuscript for Gerrit Lansing [collected poems, typescript], undated (Box 72)
    - Obituary, 2008 (Box 72)
    - Photographs and other papers, 1945-1965, undated (Box 72)
    - Poems by McGavern, copied by Lansing, 1947 (Box 72)
    - Stafford, Douglas, "Uncle Tom's Cabin" [collected poems, typescript], undated (Box 72)
  - David Rattray Papers
    David Rattray (1946-1993) was a poet and translator. He was known for his translations of French writers Antonin Arnaud, René Crevel, and Roger Gilbert-Lecomte. Among his published works are the poetry collection Opening the Eyelid, and How I Became One of the Invisible, a collection of stories and essays.
    This subseries contains typescripts of poetry, prose, and translations by David Rattray, often with inscriptions on the first page to Gerrit Lansing, as well as notes, reviews of Rattray's works, and a small amount of correspondence with Lansing.
    - "The Cloud" (collaboration with Chin Ho Cheng), undated (Box 73)
    - Ear Inn reading, poems and introduction, 1983 (Box 73)
    - "In Nomine," drafts, printed material, 1989–1990 (Box 73)
    - Letters from David Rattray to Lansing, 1979-1993, undated (Box 73)
    - Letters from Lin Rattray to Lansing, 1980-1994, undated (Box 73)
    - Material related to Benjamin Fondane, undated (Box 73)
    - Material related to Crevel's "A Difficult Death", 1986 (Box 73)
    - Misc. (photocopied photograph, etc.), undated (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous translations, 1982-1992, undated (Box 73)
    - Notes on Greece and India, undated (Box 73)
    - Obituary, memorials, tributes, 1993-1998, undated (Box 73)
    - "On Spirals" [photocopy], undated (Box 73)
    - Opening the Eyelid, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Opening the Eyelid, How I Became One of the Invisible [reviews, publicity], 1990–1993 (Box 73)
    - Poetry, 1981-1986, undated (Box 73)
    - Prose, undated (Box 73)
    - "Roger Gilbert-Lecomte" [photocopy of article, and drafts], 1984 (Box 73)
    - Translation of Antonin Artaud letters, 1983 (Box 73)
    - Translation of "Black Mirror: Poems by Roger Gilbert-Lecomte", undated (Box 74)
    - Translations of Emile Nelligan, 1988, undated (Box 74)
    - Translations of "The Pindaric Fragments of Friedrich Hölderlin", 1988 (Box 74)
    - Versions of published writings [drafts, corrected], 1983-1988, undated (Box 74)
    - The White Poem, printed version, inscribed to Gerrit Lansing, 1981 (Box 74)
  - Writings of Others
    This subseries primarily consists of typescripts of writings sent to Lansing, including poems, short stories, essays and articles, book drafts, and graduate theses; some materials contain comments by Lansing and are enclosed with correspondence. Among the authors represented are Diane di Prima, Robert Kelly, David Matlin, Robert Podgurski, Joseph Torra, and John Wieners.
    Writings of Others can also be found in Correspondence.
    - Abbot, Shep, 2000 (Box 75)
    - Abbot, Steve (photocopy), undated (Box 75)
    - Alcalay, Ammiel, 1993 (Box 75)
    - Anastas, Peter, 1995 (Box 75)
    - Bandeira, Manuel, undated (Box 75)
    - Barron, Patrick, 2007 (Box 75)
    - Basinski, Michael, undated (Box 75)
    - Behrle, Jim, undated (Box 75)
    - Bertholf, Robert, circa 2011 (Box 75)
    - Bialy, Harvey, 1971–2000 (Box 75)
    - Blackburn, Paul, undated (Box 75)
    - Blatner, Barbara, 2001 (Box 75)
    - Blevins, Rich, 1992–1999; 2 Folders (Box 75)
    - Boughn, Michael, undated (Box 75)
    - Bouchard, Daniel, 2000-2004, undated (Box 75)
    - Bowie, Ash, and Jim Dunn, undated (Box 75)
    - Brady, Andrea, 1999, undated (Box 75)
    - Broderick, John, 1969 (Box 75)
    - Byrd, Don, 2004, undated (Box 75)
    - Cedrins, Petris, 1990–1991 (Box 75)
    - Clarke, Garrett, 1989 (Box 75)
    - Clark, J. Wesley, undated (Box 75)
    - Console, Cyrus, 2011 (Box 75)
    - Cook, Amanda, 2003–2018 (Box 75)
    - Cook, James, undated (Box 75)
    - Corbett, William, undated (Box 75)
    - County, Mike, 2003–2008 (Box 75)
    - Crane, Linda, 1990–2000; 7 Folders (Box 75)
    - de la Perrière, Donna, 1998 (Box 75)
    - Dewhurst, Robert, 2006–2008 (Box 75)
    - Di Prima, Diane, 1988–2008 (Box 76)
    - Doane, Timotha, 1998–2015 (Box 77)
    - Doud, Patrick, 1997–2016; 4 Folders (Box 77)
    - Drach, Thomas, undated (Box 77)
    - Duncan, Robert and Jess (ephemera), 1963–2010 (Box 77)
    - Dunn, Jim, 2006–2016; 3 Folders (Box 77)
    - Dunn, Joe (copy of Robert Lowell's Notebook, annotated), 1971 (Box 77)
    - Dunn, Seamus, 2010 (Box 77)
    - Eberle, David, undated (Box 77)
    - Elmslie, Kenward, 1961, undated (Box 77)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1991 (Box 77)
    - Fenner, Derek, undated (Box 77)
    - Flor, Patrick, 2010 (Box 77)
    - Franco, Michael, 2002–2003 (Box 77)
    - Gallagher, Kevin, undated (Box 77)
    - Gansz, David, 1983, undated (Box 77)
    - Garcia, Edgar, undated (Box 77)
    - Gibson, Gregor, undated (Box 77)
    - Gray, Peter, 1995 (Box 77)
    - Hagerty, Tom, undated (Box 77)
    - Halevi, Tal, 2013 (Box 77)
    - Harrington, Curtis, undated (Box 77)
    - Hayes, Sewell, 2002 (Box 77)
    - Hodgson, Ralph, undated (Box 77)
    - Hollo, Anselm, 1961–1962 (Box 77)
    - Howe, Bill, undated (Box 77)
    - Irby, James, 1998–2006; 3 Folders (Box 77)
    - Irby, Kenneth, 1994–2011 (Box 77)
    - Jawdat, Nameer Ali, undated (Box 77)
    - Joris, Pierre, 2001 (Box 77)
    - Jumes, Luke, undated (Box 77)
    - Kahn, David, 1976 (Box 77)
    - Kelly, Robert, 1964–2005; 3 Folders (Box 77)
    - Kenney, Jake, undated (Box 77)
    - King, Brian, undated (Box 78)
    - Kramer, Paul and Rafael Vicente, 1998 (Box 78)
    - Lamoureux, Mark, undated (Box 78)
    - Larsson, Raymond, 1960 (Box 78)
    - Lepson, Ruth, 2012, undated (Box 78)
    - Leverkuhn, Adrian, 1999 (Box 78)
    - Lockwood, Margo, 2016 (Box 78)
    - Lockwood, Sebastian, 1998 (Box 78)
    - Longofono, Peter, 2010 (Box 78)
    - Malone, Eric, 2003-2014, undated; 2 Folders (Box 78)
    - Martin, Harry, 1961-1962, undated; 2 Folders (Box 78)
    - Martin, Zachary, 2008 (Box 78)
    - Matlin, David, 2004-2015, undated; 7 Folders (Box 78)
    - McNaughton, Duncan, 1997–2005 (Box 78)
    - Mlinko, Ange, 1996, undated (Box 78)
    - Moritz, John, 1989 (Box 78)
    - Movius, Geoffrey and Barbara, undated (Box 78)
    - Nemet-Nejat, Murat, 2002 (Box 78)
    - Newell, Kelly, undated (Box 78)
    - Norwid, Cyprian, undated (Box 78)
    - Nunnelee, Mark, 1979 (Box 78)
    - Panitz, Tamas, 2016, undated (Box 78)
    - Pawlak, Mark, 2017 (Box 78)
    - Peck, Monica / Nico, 2010 (Box 78)
    - Peterson, Tim / Trace, undated (Box 78)
    - Podgurski, Robert, 1988–2015; 10 Folders (Box 79)
    - Prygoda, Steve, 1993 (Box 79)
    - Rasula, Jed, undated (Box 79)
    - Rich, Craig, undated (Box 79)
    - Rich, David, 1998, undated (Box 79)
    - Rizzo, Chris, undated (Box 79)
    - Ryan, Paul, undated (Box 79)
    - Sawyer-Lauçanno, Christopher, undated (Box 79)
    - Scotti, Steve, undated (Box 79)
    - Shand-Tucci, Douglass, 2002 (Box 79)
    - Shively, Charley, undated (Box 79)
    - Smith, Dale, 2001, undated (Box 79)
    - Smith, Harry, 1976 (Box 79)
    - Smith, Pat, undated (Box 79)
    - Sparrow, David, undated (Box 79)
    - St. Armand, Barton, 1989 (Box 79)
    - Stefans, Brian Kim, undated (Box 79)
    - Stein, Charles, 1979-2004, undated; 5 Folders (Box 79)
    - Strong, Jonathan, 2000–2007; 3 Folders (Box 80)
    - Tarn, Nathaniel, 1998 (Box 80)
    - Torra, Joseph, 1996-2016, undated; 12 Folders (Box 80)
    - Ulansey, David, undated (Box 80)
    - Walley, Gay, 2010 (Box 80)
    - Waugh, Kyle, 2004 (Box 80)
    - Weiss, Mark, 2004 (Box 80)
    - Weston, Carol, undated (Box 80)
    - Wieners, John, 1965-2012, undated; 4 Folders (Box 80)
      Some materials are enclosed with notes by Raffael de Gruttola.
    - Wigutow, Warren, undated (Box 80)
    - Wilson, Peter Lamborn, 2004–2011; 3 Folders (Box 80)
    - Yarden, Elie, 1993 (Box 80)
    - Unidentified, 1967–1996; 3 Folders (Box 80)
  - Audiovisual and Computer Media
  - Calf, dogs, garden [reel-to-reel tape], undated (Box 81)
    Box 81 (audiovisual media): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Computer media, 2018 (Box 82)